[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my brother, George.
This is Mommy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her family
are watching
their favorite television
program, Detective Potato.
I am Detective Potato,
the world famous detective!
ALL:
Ooh!
Please help me,
Mr. Detective!
I cannot find
my flower anywhere!
Hm... Your flower is on
the top of your head!
Oh, thank you,
Mr. Detective!
[SNORTS]
That was easy!
I could do that!
Ho-ho-ho! I'm sure
you could, Peppa.
Daddy, when I grow up,
I want to be
a famous detective.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George wants to be
a detective too.
If you're going to be
detectives,
you'll each need a hat.
Detectives always wear hats.
[SNORTS]
Now you look like
two proper detectives.
[SNORTS]
And we need one of
those funny things,
that makes
everything look big.
A magnifying glass!
I think we've got one in
the kitchen drawer.
[SNORTS]
Here we are,
a real magnifying glass!
Wow!
[SNORTS]
How does it work?
You hold it in front of things
and they look bigger.
NARRATOR:
The magnifying glass makes
the little fish look big.
[SNORTS]
Can I have a go?
Wow!
NARRATOR:
The magnifying glass makes
George's eyes look very big.
[GIGGLING]
Now what you detectives need,
is a mystery to solve.
Daddy, what's
a miss-story?
A mystery
is something detectives
are good at sorting out.
[SNORTS]
Like finding lost things.
I know! We can find
George's toy dinosaur!
[SNORTS]
That's always getting
lost.
Dine-Saw!
NARRATOR:
Mr. Dinosaur is not lost.
Oh.
[SNORTS]
What about
your glasses, Daddy?
You're always
losing them.
Ho-ho-ho. Not today,
I'm wearing my glasses.
It's not fair.
There aren't any
miss-stories.
[SNORTS]
Would you like me
to make you a mystery?
Yes, please!
[SNORTING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig is going to make
a mystery.
Now.
What's on the table?
The little fish, Teddy,
a jack-in-the-box,
and Mr. Dinosaur.
[SNORTS]
That's right!
Now, look very hard and try
to remember them all.
NARRATOR:
The little fish, Teddy,
a jack-in-the-box,
and Mr. Dinosaur.
Have you
remembered them?
Yes.
[SNORTS]
Okay. You just have to go
outside for a moment.
I'll call you
when I'm ready.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT, FOOTSTEPS]
PEPPA:
It sounds like Daddy
is going upstairs...
And now he is
coming down again.
All right, you can
come back inside now.
[GIGGLES]
One thing is missing
from the table.
[SNORTS]
Do you know what?
Mr. Dinosaur is there...
little fish...
jack-in-the-box...
So who's missing?
Um... Teddy!
That's right!
Teddy's gone!
Well done,
Peppa and George!
It was quite easy
for us.
We are
famous detectives.
Ah. But that's only
half the mystery.
Where has Teddy gone?
Oh. I don't know.
What are those little
things on the floor?
They're cake crumbs.
NARRATOR:
The magnifying glass makes
the cake crumbs easy to see.
[SNORTS]
I wonder if Teddy
has been eating cake.
And the crumbs
lead this way.
[SNORTS]
Teddy's been eating
a lot of cake.
NARRATOR:
The crumbs lead into Peppa
and George's bedroom.
Oh.
The crumbs have stopped.
[SNORTS]
How can we find Teddy?
Ask me some questions.
But I will only answer
yes or no.
Okay. Um...
Is Teddy in this room?
Yes.
Is Teddy in George's bed?
No.
Is Teddy... somewhere high up?
Yes.
Teddy's in my bed!
ALL:
Hooray!
NARRATOR:
The mystery is solved.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Ho, ho! Do you still
want to be a detective
when you grow up, Peppa?
Being a detective
is quite hard.
[SNORTS]
Next time,
I want to be the one
who makes the mysteries,
like you did, Daddy.
[ALL LAUGH]
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends
are at the playground.
NARRATOR:
Peppa, Suzy and Danny
are on the roundabout.
[SNORTS]
Are you all ready?
KIDS:
Ready!
Then let's go!
[SNORTS]
Whee! Faster! Faster!
Ho, ho.
Whee! Ha-ha-ha!
NARRATOR:
George is a bit too little
for the roundabout.
He is playing on the swing.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Here is Rebecca Rabbit,
with her little brother,
Richard Rabbit.
[SQUEAKS]
Hello, everyone!
ALL: Hello!
SUZY: Baaa!
Can I come on
the roundabout too?
[SNORTS]
Hop on, Rebecca!
[GIGGLES]
Let's go really, really, fast!
[SQUEAKS]
NARRATOR:
Richard Rabbit wants to go
on the roundabout too.
Oh. If Richard gets on,
it means we can't go fast.
Richard can play
with George.
Richard, would you like
to play with George?
No!
George has a dinosaur,
just like yours.
Let's go and see.
NARRATOR:
Richard Rabbit
is the same age as George.
Richard wanted to see
George's dinosaur.
Grrr! Dine-Saw!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
George, can Richard
play with
your dinosaur?
No!
Richard, can George
play with your dinosaur?
No!
NARRATOR:
George and Richard do not want
to share their dinosaurs.
[SNORTS]
George, it will be much
more fun if you share.
That was really nice
of George.
[LAUGHS]
Dinosaur!
[SOBS]
NARRATOR:
George does not like sharing.
Richard, let George
hold the dinosaurs now.
[GIGGLES]
[CRIES]
NARRATOR:
Richard does not like
sharing either.
[BOTH CRYING]
What's all this
crying about?
George and Richard always cry
when they play together.
They're just too little
to play properly.
Can you two big girls
teach them to play together?
Of course.
We can help them
make sand castles.
Good idea! Let's go
to the sandpit!
[SNORTS]
[SQUEAKS]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR: George and Richard
love the sandpit!
[SNORTS]
George. Richard.
Today we are going
to make sand castles.
First, we fill the buckets
with sand.
We turn the buckets over,
and give them a little tap.
Now, we lift the buckets!
And presto!
NARRATOR:
Richard has made
a sand castle.
Hey, presto.
NARRATOR:
And George has made
a sand castle.
[SNORTS]
[SQUEAKS]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
DADDY PIG: You see,
[SNORTS]
playing together
is fun.
[CRIES]
[BOTH SOBBING]
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
This game has not gone
very well.
It was your brother's
fault.
[SNORTS]
He broke George's
sand castle.
[SQUEAKS]
Your brother
broke my brother's
sand castle first.
DADDY PIG:
Now, now!
You two big girls
are meant to be teaching
Richard and George
to play nicely together.
That's right.
We're big girls.
And George and Richard
are too little
to play together
properly.
Hm.
I've got an idea.
[SNORTS]
George?
What's your most favorite thing
in the whole playground?
[SNORTS]
Seesaw!
NARRATOR:
George loves the seesaw.
[LAUGHING]
Seesaw!
[SEESAW SQUEAKS]
NARRATOR:
It is a bit difficult to play
on a seesaw on your own.
[WHIMPERING]
[SQUEAKS]
NARRATOR:
Richard wants to play
on the seesaw.
[GIGGLES]
Seesaw!
Look! George and Richard
are playing together.
Seesaw!
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
George likes Richard.
[SQUEAKING, GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
Richard likes George.
George and Richard
like playing together.
[ALL LAUGHING]
♪ Seesaw seesaw ♪
[SNORTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[HORN HONKS]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are playing
at Granny and Grandpa Pig's
house today.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Hello, Grandpa Pig!
Baba Ig!
Ho! ho! Hello, Peppa.
Hello, George.
[SNORTS]
Grandpa, what
are you doing?
I'm making
a flower garden.
BOTH:
Ooh.
These seeds will grow into
beautiful flowers.
[SNORTS]
I drop the seeds
on the ground.
Then I cover the seeds
with earth.
Oh! Where have they gone?
NARRATOR:
The seeds have disappeared.
That's strange, I'm sure
I put some seeds here.
Yes, Grandpa, we saw you.
[SNORTS]
Well they're not here now.
Oh, well,
I'll just have to use
some more.
As I was saying, I simply drop
the seeds on the ground.
NARRATOR:
A little bird is eating
Grandpa Pig's flower seeds.
Oi! Get off my seeds!
[TWEETING]
So that's where
all my seeds went!
Into the little bird's tummy!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Two more little birds are
eating Grandpa Pig's seeds.
Oh! Look!
Ah! Shoo! Shoo!
[CHIRPING]
[SNORTS]
What's all this noise?
Granny Pig, the birds are
eating all my flower seeds.
So we're chasing
the birds away!
[SNORTS]
There's no point
chasing them.
They'll just
come back again. Look!
We need a scarecrow.
What's a scarecrow?
A scarecrow is a straw man
that scares birds away.
What a good idea,
Granny Pig.
[SNORTS]
I'll make one.
Come on, everyone.
Bye-bye, little birds,
we're going to make
a scarecrow.
[CHIRPING]
NARRATOR:
This is Grandpa Pig's
garden shed.
There'll be plenty of things
in here to make a scarecrow.
[SNORTS]
First, we need two sticks,
and some string.
We'll find them.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found some sticks.
George has found
some string.
Good! I'll tie the sticks
together to make the body.
NARRATOR:
Granny Pig has found some
straw and an old sack.
Lovely! I'll put the straw
in the sack to make the head.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Now the scarecrow needs
something to wear.
Here's a bag of old clothes.
PEPPA & GEORGE:
Ooh!
NARRATOR:
George has found a dress.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
Silly George!
Mr. Scarecrow doesn't want
to wear a dress.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found a coat.
Very good, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George has found a hat.
Very good, George.
Mr. Scarecrow
needs a face.
That's right. Would you and
George like to paint a face?
Yes, please.
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
George paints
the eyes and nose.
Peppa paints the mouth.
Fantastic!
NARRATOR:
Mr. Scarecrow is ready.
ALL:
Hooray!
[MUNCHING]
NARRATOR:
The little birds are looking
for Grandpa Pig's flower seeds.
Look! The little birds
are back.
Don't worry, Peppa.
Mr. Scarecrow
will scare them off.
[TWEETING]
NARRATOR:
It worked. Mr. Scarecrow has
scared the little birds away.
ALL:
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
Good.
Now my flower seeds
will not be eaten.
[TWEETING]
Oh, Grandpa.
The birds look very sad.
Yes, they must
be hungry.
That's why
I've brought this.
What's that, Granny?
It's a bird feeder.
[SNORTS]
Grandpa, may I have
some seeds, please?
[TWEETING]
Come on, birdies,
lunchtime.
[MUNCHING]
Now the birdies have
their own seeds to eat.
Hooray! The little birds
are happy again. Hee-hee!
NARRATOR:
Peppa is glad
that Grandpa Pig's seeds
will not be eaten.
But she is even more glad
that the little birds
will not be hungry.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today, Peppa is going
to the park.
ALL:
Brrr!
It's freezing
cold!
It is cold!
Brrr!
Quick! Let's get
our warm clothes on.
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
On cold days,
Peppa and her family
wear their hats
and scarves and coats.
I'll put the roof up.
[SNORTS]
Ooh, and let's get
the heating on.
[HEATER WHOOSHING]
Everyone nice and warm?
FAMILY:
Yes, Daddy Pig!
[SNORTS]
Then let's go!
[HORN HONKS]
NARRATOR: This is the park.
[SNORTS]
We're here!
ALL: Hooray!
[KIDS GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Mommy, why are all the leaves
red and yellow?
It's autumn time,
Peppa.
NARRATOR:
In the autumn,
it gets a bit colder,
and the leaves change color.
[WIND WHISTLING]
Brrr! It's quite windy.
Let's play a game
to keep warm.
[KIDS GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
My turn!
Oh. It's not meant
to go that way.
NARRATOR:
The wind is blowing
the ball along.
[QUACKING]
[SNORTS]
The ball is in
the pond.
Hm. I'll just use
this stick to reach it.
[♪♪♪]
Just a bit further,
Daddy.
[SNORTS]
Be careful, Daddy Pig...
Don't worry.
I've almost got it.
Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
[QUACKING]
Daddy, is
the water cold?
A little bit. Brrr.
[WIND WHISTLING]
NARRATOR:
The wind has blown
the ball out of the pond.
[SNORTS]
That's lucky.
Yes.
What a stroke of luck.
MOMMY PIG:
It's getting even windier.
[SNORTS]
Hold onto your hats.
NARRATOR:
Oh, no! The wind has blown
George's hat off!
[CRYING]
Don't worry George,
Daddy Pig will catch your hat!
Quick, Daddy!
[SNORTS]
[WIND CONTINUES WHISTLING]
[PANTING]
PEPPA: Look!
[SNORTS]
It's in
that little tree!
Hm. I'll just
climb up and get it.
[SNORTS]
The tree's much too thin
to take your weight,
Daddy Pig.
So how can we get
George's hat?
Simple.
I'll give the tree
a little shake.
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
Hm. Maybe if I shake it
a bit harder...
Oh!
[ALL GASP]
[SPUTTERING]
[FAMILY GIGGLING]
I thought that sort of thing
only happened to me!
[SNORTS]
It's not funny.
It is a bit funny,
Mommy.
I suppose
it is a bit funny.
[ALL LAUGH]
Where's George's hat?
[SNORTS]
It's on your head.
Ha, ha!
Here's your hat, George.
Hold onto it this time.
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
The wind is blowing all
the leaves off the trees.
Look at me! I'm leaning
into the wind! Ha, ha!
NARRATOR:
The wind is strong enough
to hold Peppa up.
[GRUNTS, GIGGLES]
NARRATOR:
The wind is strong enough
to hold George up.
[SNORTS]
Daddy! Have a go!
Uh, I'm a bit too heavy.
Come on, Daddy!
It's really fun!
Oh, all right.
NARRATOR:
The wind is strong enough
to hold up Daddy Pig.
Hee-hee-hee-hee! I say!
This is fun!
[SNORTS]
Come on, Mommy Pig!
Give it a try!
But if the wind stops,
I'll fall over.
Ho, ho!
The wind won't just stop!
NARRATOR:
The wind has stopped.
Ooh.
Hee-hee-hee-hee!
[SNORTS]
It's not funny.
It is a bit funny!
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Now the wind has stopped,
what can we do?
Hm. What's your favorite game?
Jumping up and down
in muddy puddles.
But there aren't
any puddles.
Just lots of boring,
dry leaves.
And what do you do
with dry leaves?
[SNORTS]
I don't know.
Jump up and down
in them!
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig loves jumping up
and down in leaves.
NARRATOR:
Peppa loves jumping up
and down in leaves.
Everyone loves
jumping up and down in leaves.
[ALL LAUGHING]
This is
the best autumn day ever.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]